helixsleep.com 2019-12-21

# Privacy | Helix – Helix Sleep

“Personal Information” means information that alone or when in combination with other information may be used to readily identify, contact, or locate you, such as: name, address, email address, or phone number. We do not consider Personal Information to include information that has been anonymized so that it does not allow a third party to easily identify a specific individual.

When you visit [www.helixsleep.com](http://www.helixsleep.com/) or otherwise use our Services, you are consenting to the collection,transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure, and other uses of your information as permitted by this Privacy Policy.

 **The Site Collects Your Information.**  
We collect Personal Information when you register to use the Site or other Services; use the Site or other Services; and communicate with us. We also collect information, such as anonymous usage statistics, by using cookies, server logs, and other similar technology as you use the Site.

Personal Information Collection. When you purchase a Product, you are given the option to register with the Site. If you do not register, you may checkout as a guest. In any event, when you purchase a Product, you must provide us with Personal Information, such as your name, email address, shipping address, and billing address. In addition, given that we help to customize your Products based on certain of your physical attributes, we will also ask you to provide, among other things, your height, weight, body shape match, age bracket, gender, sleeping preferences and sleeping pains/allergies.

Using the Site. We collect information you post through the Site and other Services, email or other communication. For example, when you interact with other users by posting a review, the Site will collect the information you provide in such submissions, including any Personal Information.

Making Payments. When you make payments through the Site, you may need to provide Personal Information to our third-party payment service provider, Shopify Payvments via Stripe, such as your credit card number. Additionally if you choose to use a financing option, another third-party payment service provider, Klarna, Affirm or Zibby, may ask for Personal Information. And if you choose to use another one of our third-party payment options such as Amazon Pay or PayPal, they may ask for Personal Information. For more information on the terms and privacy policies of these third-party payment service providers, please visit their websites directly.

Customer Support. We may collect Personal Information through your communications with our customer-support team. This includes phone calls, live chats, email, and social media.

Cookies, Automatic Data Collection, and Related Technologies. The Site collects and stores information that is generated automatically as you use it, including your preferences and anonymous usage statistics. You should assume that the Site can and will collect and store your on-site behavior such as pages viewed, clicks, etc in additional to information you provide directly.

When you visit the Site, we and our third-party service providers receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, and from cookies and similar technology. Cookies are small text files placed in visitors’ computer browsers to store their preferences. Most browsers allow you to block and delete cookies. However, if you do that, the Site may not work properly.

By using the Site and Services, you are authorizing us to gather, parse, and retain data related  
to the provision of the Site and Services.

By using our website, you (the visitor) agree to allow third parties to process your IP address, in order to determine your location for the purpose of currency conversion. You also agree to have that currency stored in a session cookie in your browser (a temporary cookie which gets automatically removed when you close your browser). We do this in order for the selected currency to remain selected and consistent when browsing our website so that the prices can convert to your (the visitor) local currency.

Opt-Out. As noted above, you may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer or remove them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences. Please note that cookie-based opt-outs are not effective on mobile applications. However, on many mobile devices, application users may opt out of certain mobile ads via their device settings.

The online advertising industry also provides websites from which you may opt-out of receiving targeted ads from our data partners and our other advertising partners that participate in self-regulatory programs. You can access these, and also learn more about targeted advertising and consumer choice and privacy, at [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) and[www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). You can also choose not to be included in Google Analytics by contacting us.

To be clear, whether you are using our opt-out or an online industry opt-out, these cookie-based opt-outs must be performed on each device and browser that you wish to have opted-out. For example, if you have opted out on your computer browser, that opt-out will not be effective on your mobile device. You must separately opt out on each device. We hold no liability in the event that you opt-out incorrectly or a dispute arises.

Please note that we do not respond to or honor “do not track” (a/k/a/ DNT) signals or similar mechanisms transmitted by web browsers.

 **How Helix Uses Your Information.**  
We use Personal Information to facilitate and improve our services, communicate with you and for marketing purposes.

Internal and Service-Related Usage. We may use and retain any data we collect, including Personal Information and non-personally identifiable information, and share it with third party business partners, to provide and improve our products and services, including the Products we sell and the features, functionality and usability of the Site.

Communications. We may send email to the email address you provide to us to verify your account and for informational and operational purposes, such as account management, customer service, or system maintenance.

Marketing. We may use information, including Personal Information, to facilitate transmittal of information that may be useful, relevant, valuable or otherwise of interest to you (e.g., sharing information with a third-party mattress review site with which we may partner who may seek to communicate with you in an effort to improve our products and services).

Aggregate Data. We may anonymize and aggregate data collected through the Site and use it for any purpose.

 **Helix May Disclose Your Information.**  
We may share your information with our third-party service providers; to comply with legal obligations; and to protect and defend our rights and property.

We Use Vendors and Service Providers. We may share any information we receive with vendors and service providers retained in connection with the provision of our products and services, including the Products we sell and the features, functionality and usability of the Site. We contract with various Vendors and Service Providers for services related to our business including, but not limited to, shipping, name and address verification, email distribution, market research, third party advertising, fraud prevention, promotions management, and payment processing. We may share your information, which may include Personal Information, with Vendors and Service Providers in connection with providing you with information, products or services that we think may interest you, and we or such Vendor and Service Provider may contact you about their products and/or services. We take measures to ensure to only share information they need to perform these services and never share credit card information. Additionally, we may share IP address and similar device or other automatically collected information with our Vendors and Service Providers, and as otherwise permitted by this Privacy Policy. We may also share Personal Information, anonymized information, and aggregate information with our Vendors and Service Providers who provide analytics, marketing, fulfillment, fraud detection and prevention and other services, or who may contact you about their products and services. In addition, these Vendors and Service Providers may share with us information about you that they have independently developed or acquired in accordance with their own privacy policies and practices. We may use such information for any purpose permitted by this Privacy Policy. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information with our Vendors and Service Providers for the purposes described above.

Displaying to Other Users. The content you post to the Site, email, or other communication may be displayed on the Site. Other users of the Site may be able to see some information about you, such as your name if you submit a review. We are not responsible for privacy practices of the other users who will view and use the posted information.

Marketing. We may allow access to other data collected by the Site to facilitate transmittal of information that may be useful, relevant, valuable or otherwise of interest to you (e.g., sharing information with a third-party mattress review site with which we may partner who may seek to communicate with you in an effort to improve our products and services).

As Required By Law and Similar Disclosures. We may access, preserve, and disclose your Personal Information, other account information, and content if we believe doing so is required or appropriate to comply with law enforcement requests and legal process, such as a court order or subpoena; respond to your requests; or protect yours’, ours’ or others’ rights, property, or safety.

Merger, Sale, or Other Asset Transfers. If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, financing due diligence, reorganization, bankruptcy, receivership, sale of company assets, or transition of service to another provider, then your information may be sold or transferred as part of such a transaction as permitted by law and/or contract. The use of your Personal Information following any of the foregoing events should be governed by the provisions of this Privacy Policy in effect at the time such Personal Information was collected.

 **Security of Your Information.**  
We take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us. We do not accept liability for unintentional disclosure.

By using the Site or providing Personal Information to us, you agree that we may communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of the Site. If we learn of a security system’s breach, we may attempt to notify you electronically by posting a notice on the Site or sending an e-mail to you. You may have a legal right to receive this notice in writing. To receive free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice), please notify us at [info@helixsleep.com](mailto:info@helixsleep.com).

 **Children’s Privacy.**  
We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13 and we do not want it. We will take steps to delete it if we learn we have collected it.

We do not knowingly collect, maintain, or use Personal Information from children under 13 years of age, and no part of the Site is directed to children under the age of 13. If you learn that your child has provided us with Personal Information without your consent, you may alert us at [info@helixsleep.com](mailto:info@helixsleep.com). If we learn that we have collected any Personal Information from children under 13, we will promptly take steps to delete such information and terminate the child’s account.

 **International Users.**  
By using the Site, you will transfer data to the United States.

By choosing to visit the Site or otherwise provide information to us, you agree that any dispute over privacy or the terms contained in this Privacy Policy will be governed by the laws of the State of New York, U.S.A., and the adjudication of any disputes arising in connection with Helix or the Site will be in accordance with the Terms, including binding arbitration conducted in a forum located in the State of New York.

If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use, please note that you are agreeing to the transfer of your information to the United States and processing globally. By providing your information you consent to any transfer and processing in accordance with this Policy.

 **Update your Information or Pose a Question or Suggestion.**  
If you would like to update or correct any information that you have provided to us through your use of the Site or otherwise, or if you have suggestions for improving this Privacy Policy, please send an e-mail to [info@helixsleep.com](mailto:info@helixsleep.com).

 **Changes to Our Privacy Policy and Practices.**  
We may revise this Privacy Policy, so review it periodically. Posting of Revised Privacy Policy. We will post any adjustments to the Privacy Policy on this web page, and the revised version will be effective when it is posted. If you are concerned about how your information is used, bookmark this page and read this Privacy Policy periodically.

Contact Information  
Helix Sleep, Inc.  
1123 Broadway, #600  
New York, NY 10010
